<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Anecdote</string>
    <string name="test">test</string>

    <string name="submit">Submit</string>

    <string name="register_here">
        <u>Register here</u>
    </string>

    <string name="empty_check">Empty check</string>
    <string name="email_check">Email check</string>
    <string name="digit_check">Digit check</string>
    <string name="value_check">Value check</string>
    <string name="no_check">No check</string>

    <string name="error_message_empty">Please fill this field</string>
    <string name="error_message_email">Please input a valid email address</string>
    <string name="error_message_digit">Please input digits only</string>
    <string name="error_message_password">Length 6–12 characters. Only letters and numbers allowed.</string>

    <string name="first_name">First Name</string>
    <string name="last_name">Last Name</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="email">Email Address</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="email_detail">email detail</string>
    <string name="first_name_detail">first name detail</string>
    <string name="id_detail">id detail</string>
    <string name="last_name_detail">last name detail</string>
    <string name="password_detail">password detail</string>
    <string name="username_detail">username detail</string>
    <string name="placeholder_image">placeholder image</string>
    <string name="category_name">Category Name</string>
    <string name="category_image">Category Image</string>
    <string name="send_to">Share persuasive story via:</string>

    <!-- START STORY FORM -->
    <string name="storyCreateMetaFirst">Create a New Story:\nThink the Audience First</string>
    <string name="welcomeMessageMetaFirst">OK! It is time to create a <b>persuasive</b> story.
        \nA persuasive story is a story that aims to <b>influence</b>.
        \n\nIn most cases the audience is more persuaded from stories that describe an <b>issue</b> and its <b>potential resolution</b>.
        So when writing your story you should have in mind your <b>audience</b> so you can make the story <b>relatable</b> to them as much as possible.
        This makes the story more influential to them.
        \n\nTalking about influence you should be aiming to <b>change</b> some aspect of your audience\'s personality. This could be
        their <b>knowledge/understanding</b> regarding an issue, their <b>attitude</b> towards it, their <b>intention</b> to do something about it and ultimately a potential positive <b>behaviour</b> relevant to it.
        \n\nIn order for you to make your story more relatable Anecdot will guide you through a series of steps that will help you to tailor your story according to your audience.\n
    </string>

    <string name="categoryMetaFirst">To begin with, select the <b><font color="#B2182D">topic</font></b> in which your story fits. By selecting one of the topics provided (or by suggesting your own), you are directly
        targeting people that are interested to read a relevant story. This will also give you some specific tips later on.</string>
    <string name="stageMetaFirst">Secondly, the state that your audience is in greatly affects their perception of your story in general and of your intended message.
        \n\nThe audience typically moves through <b>4 main stages</b> in order to change.  While thinking of the problem or issue your story will be about, select the <b><font color="#128E4A">stage</font></b>
        in which your intended audience would most likely belong in regard to the issue.</string>
    <string name="swipeRightMetaFirst">According to what you have selected, tailored suggestions have been generated for you. You can <b>swipe right</b>
        and get extra information on how to make your story more relatable and thus more persuasive for your audience. Specific <b>goals and strategies</b>
        are available according to your selections. Your persuasive story will be a combination of these persuasive factors and a narrative that will be structured within them to
        help deliver your message.
        \n\nYou could try to <b>promote an idea</b> to create change and move your audience to action or you can just <b>describe something important to you</b> and why is should matter to them as well.
        Anything goes, from a <b>hero\'s journey</b>, to a story of <b>personal growth</b> that have changed your worldview.
    </string>

    <string name="guidanceMetaFirst">Now think about your audience in relation to the <b><font color="#128E4A">stage</font></b> they are in.
        \n- How can you make the <b>stage goal</b> suggested in the tips section relevant to them?
        \n- Which <b>strategies</b> will more likely work for them?
        \n\nUse the field below to capture your ideas. You will be able to rearrange these later when editing your story.</string>
    <string name="stageRelatedHint">Making the story relatable: stage.</string>

    <string name="guidance2MetaFirst">Think about the <b><font color="#B2182D">topic/theme/area</font></b> of your story.
        \n- Is it relatable to your intended audience?
        \n- How does this affect the setting
        and actors of the story?
        \n\nUse the field below to capture any related ideas. You will be able to rearrange them later when editing your story.</string>
    <string name="contextRelatedHint">Making the story relatable: topic.</string>

    <string name="guidance3MetaFirst">If \'Other\' was selected please give a suggested topic or give extra keywords for your story.</string>
    <string name="ifOtherSpecifyMetaFirst">Suggested topic or extra keywords.</string>

    <string name="beforeTitleMetaFirst">Next we will start thinking of the content of the narrative around which our persuasive story is constructed. Each compelling story needs to start somewhere.
        \nGive a <b>title</b> and a <b>short description</b>for your story/idea. You can always change it later.</string>
    <string name="titleMetaFirst">Give the title of your story.</string>
    <string name="storyDescriptionMetaFirst">Quickly summarise your story in one line.</string>

    <string name="beforeOrientationMetaFirst">Now it is time for you to <b>set the scene</b> and give the background for your story. It should be written in a way
        that the audience might find relevant and relatable.
        \n- <b>Who</b> is involved in the story?
        \n- <b>When</b> did the events take place? - <b>Where</b>?
        \n- <b>How</b> were the actors/people in the story feeling and acting?
        \n- <b>Why</b> the situation was like that?
        \n\nThis information will be used to bring your audience close to what you are describing.</string>
    <string name="orientationMetaFirst">Set the scene/background.</string>


    <string name="beforeComplicatedActionMetaFirst">In the next part you will describe what actually happens in the story. As mentioned before the audience is more likely to be influenced
        by stories that describe an <b>issue</b> and its <b>potential resolution</b> through the story.
        \n- You could describe a <b>problem/challenge/obstacle/issue</b>
        that your audience, you or someone else you are trying to influence struggles with now or in the past.</string>
    <string name="complicatedActionMetaFirst">What happens in the story? What is the issue?</string>

    <string name="beforeEvaluationMetaFirst">The next part is used for you to describe <b>why you chose to share</b> the story.
        \n- Why do you think it is <b>important/interesting</b>?
        \n- Why are you <b>excited/passionate</b> about it?
        \n- You could describe how the people in the story felt.
        \n- You could also describe a better world where the issue does not exist.
        \n- You could talk about what was difficult, or the steps taken to tackle the issue.</string>
    <string name="evaluationMetaFirst">Why is this interesting/important/exciting?</string>

    <string name="beforeResolutionMetaFirst">Now it is time to describe <b>what finally happened</b> in the story.
        \n- You can write about how the issue was <b>resolved</b> or how the people in their story accomplished their goals.
        \n- Did they succeed or fail? Was there a twist or something unexpected?</string>
    <string name="resolutionMetaFirst">Describe what happened in the end.</string>

    <string name="beforeMessageMetaFirst">The next part is very important for your story to be persuasive. It gives you the opportunity to leave your audience with the
        <b><font color="#8E44AD">meaning or significance</font></b> of what happened.
        \n- You can describe how after the issue has been resolved the world is a better place for the people in the story.
        \n- You could share <b>strategies</b> and give <b>suggestions</b> to your audience and reinforce of <b>why these are relevant</b> to them.
        \n- You could write about how the audience\'s life will improve after following your suggestions along perhaps with how this experience changed you.
        \n- You could <b>give a key takeaway lesson</b> and connect it to your audience\'s lives.
        \n- You could also share <b>scenarios or examples</b> that would nudge your audience
        to apply what they have learned.</string>
    <string name="messageMetaFirst">What should the audience take away?</string>

    <string name="beforeReview">OK! Now we are ready to put all the elements of your persuasive story together.
        \n You can click the generate button to create your persuasive story. You will be able to edit your persuasive story after generating it. You can always come back to this screen to get tips but</string>


    <string name="beforeUrlMetaFirst">You can use the button below to generate your <b>persuasive story</b> based your previous inputs.
        \n\nAs mentioned before your story consists of persuasive factors related to the <b><font color="#B2182D">topic</font></b> of the story and the <b><font color="#128E4A">stage</font></b> that your audience is in
        as well as a <b><font color="#000000">narrative</font></b> that these will be structured around. Your takeaway <b><font color="#8E44AD">message</font></b> for your audience is also presented in the end.
        \n\nThe content is colour coded so it is easier to identify the elements even if these are rearranged in the story. The final story will not be coloured, it is simply for your convenience while editing. You can freely edit your story in the field provided below to make it more coherent, fluent and relatable to your audience. Sections can be cut/copy-pasted and new information can be added.
        \n\n<b>Attention!</b> It is best to complete all the fields above before attempting to generate your persuasive story. This will be essential when attempting to save your story in the end.</string>
    <string name="urlMetaFirst">Generate and edit your persuasive story.</string>

    <string name="review_story">Preview and Post Online</string>
    <string name="save_story">Save Story</string>
    <string name="update_story">Preview and Update</string>
    <!-- END STORY FORM -->


    <string name="register">register</string>

    <!-- User area strings -->
    <string name="send_user_details">Share user details via:</string>
    <string name="scroll_right_tip_links_tutorials">Remember to scroll right to get your story tip of the day and access to useful links and tutorials.</string>
    <string name="dashboard_intro_text">Jump straight into the story!</string>
    <string name="create_storyTop"><b>Create a Story</b></string>
    <string name="create_story">Full Guidance</string>
    <string name="read_storyTop"><b>Read a Story</b></string>
    <string name="read_story">By Topic</string>
    <string name="my_favourites">My Favourites</string>
    <string name="story_categories">Story Categories</string>
    <string name="intro_TipOTD">Here is today\'s tip for more impactful and influential stories!</string>
    <string name="generate_tip">I want another tip!</string>
    <string name="intro_links_tutorials">Here you can find useful links and video tutorials for persuasive writing.</string>
    <!-- User area strings end-->

    <!-- Tip of the day -->
    <string-array name="string_array_TipOTD">
        <item>Take a stance. What do you think about the issue? What side will you take? Be aware of any prejudices you might have that could color your argument. What resolution will you suggest?</item>
        <item>Know your audience. Determine if your audience will agree with your position and why they may not. You must be able to understand both sides of the issue in order to successfully argue your point of view.</item>
        <item>Thoroughly research your topic. The point of a persuasive essay is to provide detailed and compelling evidence—you should be able to disprove the opposing argument. It will likely be necessary to undertake library-based research in order to accomplish this.</item>
        <item>Think about the structure of your essay. Determine what evidence you will include and the order in which you will present it. Remember, it must be logical.</item>
        <item>Support your argument. Use hard facts. You can gather these from your research, observations, or personal experiences. But be careful! In order to avoid plagiarism, you must cite your sources. You should always use verifiable statistics. It is important to be able to back up your argument with data. In order to further strengthen the argument in your persuasive essay, try using one or two direct quotes from experts on the topic. Finally, provide meaningful examples to enhance and clearly illustrate your argument.</item>
        <item>Create rapport with the person you are trying to influence – it may sound like common sense but if they like and trust you there is a greater possibility that you will be able to persuade them.</item>
        <item>Focus On Your Best Audience. Writers tend to cast a wide net, hoping to influence everyone. However, focusing on the people who are most likely to benefit from the content and writing for them will bring better results.</item>
        <item>Tell Them Why. Readers are constantly bombarded with messages on a daily basis. If you want their attention, justify it with a good reason up front, preferably something that will benefit them.</item>
        <item>Be Authoritative. Establish yourself as an authority up front and be consistent in backing up that authority with proof, statistics and examples. Be honest and transparent, don’t waver, and pretty soon your audience will believe you.</item>
        <item>Take The Reader’s Point of View. If you were the reader, what would grab your attention? When you are writing persuasive copy, you have to become the reader to understand what appeals to them.</item>
        <item>Show That You Understand. Before you can persuade your reader, you must establish that you are just like them in some way. Perhaps you share the same problem or have similar desires. Find a mutual connection and state it early on.</item>
        <item>Tell Both Sides of the Story. There is always another side of the story. Unlike addressing objections, telling the other side of the story allows you to paint a compelling picture of what life would be like without your product or service. It would be awful. Tell them.</item>
        <item>Use Influential Words. To write persuasive copy, use persuasive “action” words like miracle, discovery, discount, and bargain. Use uplifting words like vitality, grace, wisdom, and confidence. Finally, make sure your copy has ‘Free’, ’How’, ’New’ and ‘You’ in abundance.</item>
        <item>Simplify and Amplify. Simplify your core ideas into hard-hitting individual thoughts, then amplify them with the help of things that are important to the reader. Use words that help empower your readers. Get! Learn! Results! Now!</item>
        <item>Be Repetitive. If you’ve said it once, you can say it again. Repetition is a time-honored tactic for remembering anything. Use it to your advantage.</item>
        <item>Address Objections. Even the most agreeable readers will likely have objections, and you are much better off addressing them up front than waiting for your potential customer to voice them. This is another means of establishing authority, and also tells your reader that you have thought the matter through.</item>
        <item>Show Proof. As previously mentioned, showing proof helps establish you as an authority on the subject, and shows your reader that you respect them.</item>
        <item>Focus on Headline Psychology. Headlines matter. If the headline is not catchy enough for a click, the rest of the content will fall flat. Make sure that the headline is psychologically stimulating and interesting to your readers. However, don’t sacrifice clarity for the sake of flash. Your headlines should be catchy but concise.</item>
        <item>Be Consistent. State your position up front, then proceed to be unfailingly consistent in backing it up with facts, stats and proof. Essentially, you want your readers to trust you. A reader who trusts you will tend to agree with you, and nothing builds trust more effectively than being consistent.</item>
        <item>Use Simple Language. Don’t overload your content. Write as simply as possible. Make your message accessible to every reader. Don’t use complex terminology unless you need to. If you do need to, explain it in simple words.</item>
        <item>Be Precise. People love details. Using detail in your writing shows that you’re a person who really knows what you’re writing about – a person to be trusted. Be as specific as you can. Visibility and accessibility should be your main principles.</item>
        <item>“Sir! Yes, Sir!” Use all of your imagination to create a situation in which the reader will agree with you. It’s very easy to do. Make some general statements or ask questions that are difficult to challenge. Ask questions where the only possible answer is YES.</item>
        <item>Predict Your Reader. Anticipate the questions of the reader, and answer them before they’re even asked – before they’ve even thought about. Neutralize possible questions before they even appear. Comprehensive information is exactly what your reader is looking for.</item>
        <item>Prove it! It’s easy to write persuasive text if you can back up your claims with facts and studies. Numbers and percentages have the best effect. They’re your strongest tools for convincing readers.</item>
        <item>Be Specific. Use real-life examples. We believe in examples we can relate to. It’s easy to say: “Do this, do that.” But how can you apply it in real life? Examples from the real world make material understandable. They make readers think, “If someone else achieved this, why can\'t I?”</item>
        <item>Touch the Emotions. Evoke emotion in the reader. As we know, emotions are the main motivation behind making a purchases or sealing a business deal. Emotions awaken desire. As Napoleon Hill said: “The starting point of all achievement is desire.”</item>
        <item>Use Greatness. Cite great wisdom. Well-chosen quotes from successful people will elevate your text to the next level. A couple of good quotes from well-known experts in the field will help you to make your material more compelling.</item>
        <item>Use Structure. Divide your articles into paragraphs, headings, subheadings and lists. These increase the visual appeal of the text. Paragraphs should contain between 2 and 5 sentences, and no more. That will make it much easier for your reader to digest your material.</item>
        <item>Make it Right. The web is littered with low-quality content. No matter how interesting and useful your text is, grammatical errors will spoil the impression of your content – and give a bad impression of the author. Text with grammatical errors is like a road with potholes. In order to write well, read a lot. Use your dictionary, spell check and grammar check. Brush up on your school rules. Have someone proofread your article. And keep writing.</item>
        <item>Draw Your Text. If you can express your idea in a few pictures, rather than 10 paragraphs of text, use the pictures! What would you rather share on social networks – a picture or a link to text? Infographics are a great way to get your ideas across. Modern readers are reluctant to spend a lot of time reading, but they’re quick to register and interpret visual information.</item>
        <item>Use Your Imagination. Writing that tells a story makes is so much more special than that which is only informative. Story-telling awakens our imagination and makes your message relatable to the reader. It’s also far more interesting to read. Use words such as “imagine”, “see” and “remember”.</item>
    </string-array>
    <!-- Tip of the day end -->

    <!-- LINKS -->
    <string name="link1">Guide: <a href="https://problogger.com/th-science-of-storytelling-6-ways-to-write-more-persuasive-stories/">6 Ways to Write More Persuasive Stories</a></string>
    <string name="link2">Article: <a href="https://hbr.org/2011/03/using-stories-as-a-tool-of-per">Using Stories to Persuade</a></string>
    <string name="link3">Article: <a href="https://www.hrzone.com/talent/retention/how-to-use-storytelling-to-influence-people">How to use storytelling to influence people</a></string>
    <string name="link4"><a href="http://www.www.com">ForGet Password</a></string>
    <string name="link5"><a href="http://www.www.com">ForGet Password</a></string>

    <!-- Stage labels -->
    <string name="precontemplation_info">I want to know more</string>
    <string name="contemplation_info">I am thinking to change</string>
    <string name="preparation_info">I want to do something soon</string>
    <string name="action_info">I am already trying</string>
    <string name="default_info">Not defined</string>
    <!-- Stage labels end-->

    <string name="write_story_notification_title_template">Write story: %1$s</string>

    <!-- TODO: remove this placeholder text -->
    <string name="write_story_notification_placeholder_text_template">You said %1$s and lorem ipsum
        dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit. Etiam non enim magna. Morbi dictum, velit vel
        semper venenatis, magna odio volutpat velit, at ullamcorper nulla lacus sed turpis.
        Pellentesque vitae metus elit, nec tincidunt tellus. Integer sed nisl sem, ullamcorper
        ornare lacus. Duis ac mauris sed massa congue volutpat. Donec sed erat sit amet turpis
        viverra rhoncus sit amet nec magna. Donec lacinia ligula at libero volutpat volutpat nec nec
        tortor.
    </string>

    <!-- Notifications -->
    <string name="sett_reminder_header">Set notification for story nudge</string>
    <string name="sett_reminder_label">Sometimes we simply forget that important things happened during the day
     and good ideas that we had are not used make a change. With Anecdote you can set a gentle nudge at a
    convenient time for you (e.g. when you are comfy at home) to start writing a compelling story. Practice
    makes perfect so try to write often and share your world-changing ideas!</string>
    <string name="sett_reminder_desc">Flick the switch to enable/disable notifications.</string>
    <string name="sett_reminder_time_label">Set Reminder Time</string>
    <string name="sett_reminder_time_content">8 : 00 PM</string>

    <!-- Stages Fragment -->
    <string name="stage_default">Default Information</string>
    <string name="stage_default_label">Something was not properly selected, please go back and select a stage in the relevant spinner.
    \n\nBut since you are here you could perhaps benefit from some general information on how to write a persuasive story.
    \n- Start with a <b>logical argument</b> in regard to a problem or issue.
    \n- You should also give <b>suggestions and strategies</b> to show to your audience <b>what they should</b> do in regard to the issue.
    \n- You should explain <b>why</b> they should do that and <b>what they will gain</b> if they do so.
    \n\nRemember your goal is to construct a <b>persuasive argument</b> to help them move from the fence!
    \n\n\nAlso here are the top 5 impactful words in the English language: <b>You, Because, Free, Instantly, New</b>
    \nUse them wisely!</string>

    <string name="stage_1">Stage 1: Before Thinking</string>
    <string name="stage_1_label"><font color="#d21414"><b>\nInformation: </b></font>In this stage the audience is <b>unaware</b> of the problem/issue that you are describing.
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Change potential: </b></font>They <b>don\'t have the intention to make a change</b> in relation to it in the foreseeable future (e.g. 6 months).
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Example: </b></font>First time smokers that do not know the dangers of smoking fall into this category.\n</string>
    <string name="stage_1_goal">Your goal in this stage is:</string>
    <string name="stage_1_goal_label">- To make them <b>aware</b> of the problem or issue.
        \n- Suggest specific <b>examples and strategies</b> for your audience. \n</string>
    <string name="stage_1_strategies">Strategies of Change</string>
    <string name="get_the_facts"><b>Get the facts</b></string>
    <string name="get_the_facts_label">This strategy aims to mainly change <b>knowledge and understanding</b> of the audience
    in regard to themselves and the problem/issue or the intended message.
        \n\n<b>You can help them by:</b>
        \n- Making relevant observations
        \n- Showcasing confrontations between actors in the story
        \n- Elaborating on your interpretations of the situation
        \n- Suggesting relevant sources of information for them to educate themselves
        \n\n<b>They will:</b>
        \n- Find and learn new facts, ideas and tips that support change\n
    </string>
    <string name="pay_attention_to_feelings"><b>Pay attention to feelings</b></string>
    <string name="pay_attention_to_feelings_label">The goal here is to have your audience <b>experience and express feelings</b> about problems and
        their potential solutions. The audience tends to <b>connect to a character</b> in a story that they feel they can relate to and <b>transfer the
            character\'s emotions to themselves</b>.
    \n\n<b>You can help them by:</b>
        \n- Drawing attention to the characters and their feelings through situations in your story that makes them contemplate loss
        \n- Providing hints that make them connect and re-dramatise the situation into their daily lives
        \n- Influencing them to immerse into a different role into the story
    \n\n<b>They will:</b>
        \n- Experience negative emotions in relation to the problem/issue (e.g. fear, anxiety, worry)
        \n- Link these negative emotions to the undesired behaviour (the one you want them to move away from)\n</string>
    <string name="notice_your_effect_on_others"><b>Notice your effect on others</b></string>
    <string name="notice_your_effect_on_others_label">This is meant to make your audience <b>assess how their individual problem/issue affects their environment.</b>
     \n\n<b>You can help them by:</b>
        \n- Addressing them directly in the story or vicariously via the actor of the story
        \n- Giving examples in combinations with facts
        \n- Explicitly stating the feelings of different sides for empathy training
    \n\n<b>They will:</b>
        \n- Realise the positive/negative impact they potentially have to their environment\n</string>
    <string name="notice_public_support"><b>Notice public support</b></string>
    <string name="notice_public_support_label">This strategy is meant to showcase the importance of incorporating in the story the
    <b>social and societal</b> aspect of the problem/issue.
    \n\n<b>You can help them by:</b>
        \n- Making them realise that the desired behaviour is preferred by their circles and the society overall
        \n- Advocating for a specific aspect, empower your audience by stating the universality of the support
        \n- Pointing to relevant policy campaigns and interventions
    \n\n<b>They will:</b>
        \n- Understand and potentially attempt to follow the socially desirable path (adhere to social norms)</string>

    <string name="stage_2">Stage 2: Thinking</string>
    <string name="stage_2_label"><font color="#d21414"><b>\nInformation: </b></font>In this stage the audience is <b>aware</b> of the problem/issue that you are describing.
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Change potential: </b></font>They are <b>seriously considering to make a change</b> in relation to it in the foreseeable future (e.g. 6 months).
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Example: </b></font> People that have been diagnosed with respiratory problems due to smoking fall into this category.\n</string>
    <string name="stage_2_goal_label">- To change the <b>intention to act</b> of your audience.
        \n- Show that the cons of changing towards the desired behaviour are not that many.\n</string>
    <string name="create_a_new_self_image"><b>Create a new self image</b></string>
    <string name="create_a_new_self_image_label">This strategy aims to make the audience assess how they feel and think about themselves with respect to the problem.
    \n\n<b>You can help them by:</b>
        \n- Showing them potential corrective emotional experiences of the actors
        \n- Showing them through story imagery important values to them
    \n\n<b>They will:</b>
        \n- Re-evaluate themselves and help clarify/consolidate their values.\n</string>

    <string name="stage_3">Stage 3: Preparing to Act</string>
    <string name="stage_3_label"><font color="#d21414"><b>\nInformation: </b></font>In this stage the audience is <b>may have already taken some steps</b> towards the desired behaviour.
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Change potential: </b></font>They are <b>intending to take action</b> in regard the problem/issue that you are describing very soon (e.g. next 30 days).
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Example: </b></font>People that know about the benefits of exercising and want to lose weight, but they are postponing to sign up for the gym fall into this category.\n</string>
    <string name="stage_3_goal_label">- To actually make them act by showing that they <b>can</b> change.
        \n- Give them the required nudge to <b>go from thinking to acting</b>.\n</string>
    <string name="make_a_commitment"><b>Make a commitment</b></string>
    <string name="make_a_commitment_label">The purpose of this strategy is to make your audience <b>believe that they have the ability to change.</b>
    \n\n<b>You can help them by:</b>
        \n- Reassuring them that they can do it
        \n- Showing that a relatable character in your story can do it
        \n- Suggesting to your audience to commit to action
        \n- Giving specific examples of resolutions to assist their decision making process
    \n\n<b>They will:</b>
        \n- Strengthen their commitments in order to achieve self-liberation\n</string>
    <string name="get_support"><b>Get Support</b></string>
    <string name="get_support_label">The goal of this strategy is to encourage the audience to be <b>open and trusting</b> about the problem/issue with someone who cares.
    \n\n<b>You can help them by:</b>
        \n- Encouraging them to seek social support from their circles
        \n- Showing them how to form theurapeutic alliances with their peers
    \n\n<b>They will:</b>
        \n- Potentially turn to self-help and social media groups that can assist in that aspect\n</string>
    <string name="use_substitutes"><b>Use substitutes</b></string>
    <string name="use_substitutes_label">This process of change is important because it <b>aims to substitute problematic behaviours with desired alternatives.</b>
    \n\n<b>You can help them by:</b>
        \n- Making them relax and desensitise in regard of the problematic outcomes
        \n- Giving them examples and suggestions to increase their confidence towards achieving the desired outcomes
    \n\n<b>They will:</b>
        \n- Be more assertive and positive about themselves and their capabilities\n</string>

    <string name="stage_4">Stage 4: Acting</string>
    <string name="stage_4_label"><font color="#d21414"><b>\nInformation: </b></font>In this stage the audience is <b>currently modifying their behaviour, experiences and/or environment</b> to overcome the issue/problem.
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Change potential: </b></font>They have <b>overtly changed their behaviour</b> for some time (less than 6 months).
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Example: </b></font>People that have committed to a diet, go to the gym but are victims of the occasional food temptation fall into this category.\n</string>
    <string name="stage_4_goal_label">- To help them gain the <b>self-confidence</b> needed to maintain the positive outcome of their efforts (consolidate their gains).
        \n- Potentially <b>prevent relapse</b> to undesirable behaviours.\n</string>
    <string name="manage_the_environment"><b>Manage the environment</b></string>
    <string name="manage_the_environment_label">This process of change aims to teach the audience to <b>control situations and other causes that trigger problematic behaviours</b>.
    \n\n<b>You can help them by:</b>
        \n- Suggesting stimuli that encourage alternative desired behaviours
        \n- Providing guidance through your story to help them arrange their environment in order to counter stimuli that trigger undesirable behaviours
    \n\n<b>They will:</b>
        \n- Learn to avoid high risk cues and to employ fading techniques to them\n</string>
    <string name="rewarding_oneself_or_being_rewarded_by_others_for_making_changes"><b>Rewarding oneself or being rewarded by others for making changes</b></string>
    <string name="rewarding_oneself_or_being_rewarded_by_others_for_making_changes_label">This strategy of change aims to help the audience <b>manage overt and covert reinforcement.</b>
        \n\n<b>You can help them by:</b>
        \n- Showing through the characters of the story the overt benefits of the desired behaviour
        \n- Encouraging them to self-reward
        \n- Suggesting contingency contracts (benefits-consequences for meeting or failing to achieve the desired behaviour)
    \n\n<b>They will:</b>
        \n- Learn to appreciate the increased rewards of the positive behaviour in contrast to the decreased rewards of the undesired behaviour\n
    </string>
    <!-- End of Stages fragment -->

    <!-- Help and support Activity -->
    <string name="help_and_support">Help and Support</string>
    <string name="help_description">\nIn case of a bug, issue or any other kind of assistance please use the button below to contact me.</string>
    <string name="timer_icon">timer icon</string>
    <string name="report_a_problem">Report a problem</string>
    <!-- End of Help and Support Activity -->

    <!-- Category/Topic Fragment -->
    <string name="default_topic">Default Topic</string>
    <string name="stage_default_info">\nSomething was not properly selected, please go back and select a stage in the relevant spinner.
    \n\nBut since you are here you could perhaps benefit from some general information on how to write a persuasive story.
    \n- Start with a <b>logical argument</b> in regard to a problem or issue.
    \n- You should also give <b>suggestions and strategies</b> to show to your audience <b>what they should</b> do in regard to the issue.
    \n- You should explain <b>why</b> they should do that and <b>what they will gain</b> if they do so.
    \n\nRemember your goal is to construct a <b>persuasive argument</b> to help them move from the fence!
    \n\n\nAlso here are the top 5 impactful words in the English language: <b>You, Because, Free, Instantly, New</b>
    \nUse them wisely!</string>
    <string name="topic_default_info">\nSomething was not properly selected, please go back and select a topic in the relevant spinner.
    \n\nBut since you are here you could perhaps benefit from some general information on how to write a persuasive story.
    \n- Start with a <b>logical argument</b> in regard to a problem or issue.
    \n- You should also give <b>suggestions and strategies</b> to show to your audience <b>what they should</b> do in regard to the issue.
    \n- You should explain <b>why</b> they should do that and <b>what they will gain</b> if they do so.
    \n\nRemember your goal is to construct a <b>persuasive argument</b> to help them move from the fence!
    \n\n\nAlso here are the top 5 impactful words in the English language: <b>You, Because, Free, Instantly, New</b>
    \nUse them wisely!</string>
    <string name="other">Other</string>
    <string name="other_information">\nAs mentioned before, the <b>topic</b> of your story is very important in order for your audience to relate to it. Remember,
        a <b>more relatable story</b> is <b>more impactful</b> and <b>more persuasive</b> so your goal is to achieve exactly that. Try to make your audience immerse in your story and transport to your setting.
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Think of your audience: </b></font>
        \n- <b>Who</b> are they?
        \n- <b>Why</b> are they would be particularly interested in this topic?
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Think of your story: </b></font>
        \n- Who are the <b>characters</b> in your story? Can your audience relate to them? Will you be able to show desired and undesired behaviours through your characters to influence your audience?
        \n- <b>Where and when</b> does the story take place? Is this context/setting something that you audience could visualise themselves in? Does it fit to the problem/issue that you are trying to describe?
        \n- <b>How</b> do your characters/actors act and interact with each other? What state are they in? Will your audience be able to relate to this behavioural situation?
        \n- Are there any <b>specific constraints</b> you should consider that relate to the topic of the story that you should set?
        \n\n<font color="#d21414">You can use the <b>topic field in your story form</b>  to start taking notes on making the story more relatable using its topic.</font>
    </string>
    <string name="art">Art</string>
    <string name="art_information">\nAs mentioned before, the <b>topic</b> of your story is very important in order for your audience to relate to it. Remember,
        a <b>more relatable story</b> is <b>more impactful</b> and <b>more persuasive</b> so your goal is to achieve exactly that. Try to make your audience immerse in your story and transport to your setting.
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Think of your audience: </b></font>
        \n- <b>Who</b> are they?
        \n- <b>Why</b> are they would be particularly interested in this topic?
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Think of your story: </b></font>
        \n- Who are the <b>characters</b> in your story? Can your audience relate to them? Will you be able to show desired and undesired behaviours through your characters to influence your audience?
        \n- <b>Where and when</b> does the story take place? Is this context/setting something that you audience could visualise themselves in? Does it fit to the problem/issue that you are trying to describe?
        \n- <b>How</b> do your characters/actors act and interact with each other? What state are they in? Will your audience be able to relate to this behavioural situation?
        \n- Are there any <b>specific constraints</b> you should consider that relate to the topic of the story that you should set?
        <!--
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Specific for Art: </b></font>
        \n- <b>Who</b> are they?
        -->
        \n\n<font color="#d21414">You can use the <b>topic field in your story form</b>  to start taking notes on making the story more relatable using its topic.</font>
    </string>
    <string name="causes">Causes</string>
    <string name="causes_information">\nAs mentioned before, the <b>topic</b> of your story is very important in order for your audience to relate to it. Remember,
        a <b>more relatable story</b> is <b>more impactful</b> and <b>more persuasive</b> so your goal is to achieve exactly that. Try to make your audience immerse in your story and transport to your setting.
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Think of your audience: </b></font>
        \n- <b>Who</b> are they?
        \n- <b>Why</b> are they would be particularly interested in this topic?
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Think of your story: </b></font>
        \n- Who are the <b>characters</b> in your story? Can your audience relate to them? Will you be able to show desired and undesired behaviours through your characters to influence your audience?
        \n- <b>Where and when</b> does the story take place? Is this context/setting something that you audience could visualise themselves in? Does it fit to the problem/issue that you are trying to describe?
        \n- <b>How</b> do your characters/actors act and interact with each other? What state are they in? Will your audience be able to relate to this behavioural situation?
        \n- Are there any <b>specific constraints</b> you should consider that relate to the topic of the story that you should set?
        <!--
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Specific for Causes: </b></font>
        \n- <b>Who</b> are they?
        -->
        \n\n<font color="#d21414">You can use the <b>topic field in your story form</b>  to start taking notes on making the story more relatable using its topic.</font>
    </string>
    <string name="education">Education</string>
    <string name="education_information">\nAs mentioned before, the <b>topic</b> of your story is very important in order for your audience to relate to it. Remember,
        a <b>more relatable story</b> is <b>more impactful</b> and <b>more persuasive</b> so your goal is to achieve exactly that. Try to make your audience immerse in your story and transport to your setting.
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Think of your audience: </b></font>
        \n- <b>Who</b> are they?
        \n- <b>Why</b> are they would be particularly interested in this topic?
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Think of your story: </b></font>
        \n- Who are the <b>characters</b> in your story? Can your audience relate to them? Will you be able to show desired and undesired behaviours through your characters to influence your audience?
        \n- <b>Where and when</b> does the story take place? Is this context/setting something that you audience could visualise themselves in? Does it fit to the problem/issue that you are trying to describe?
        \n- <b>How</b> do your characters/actors act and interact with each other? What state are they in? Will your audience be able to relate to this behavioural situation?
        \n- Are there any <b>specific constraints</b> you should consider that relate to the topic of the story that you should set?
        <!--
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Specific for Education: </b></font>
        \n- <b>Who</b> are they?
        -->
        \n\n<font color="#d21414">You can use the <b>topic field in your story form</b>  to start taking notes on making the story more relatable using its topic.</font>
    </string>
    <string name="food">Food</string>
    <string name="food_information">\nAs mentioned before, the <b>topic</b> of your story is very important in order for your audience to relate to it. Remember,
        a <b>more relatable story</b> is <b>more impactful</b> and <b>more persuasive</b> so your goal is to achieve exactly that. Try to make your audience immerse in your story and transport to your setting.
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Think of your audience: </b></font>
        \n- <b>Who</b> are they?
        \n- <b>Why</b> are they would be particularly interested in this topic?
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Think of your story: </b></font>
        \n- Who are the <b>characters</b> in your story? Can your audience relate to them? Will you be able to show desired and undesired behaviours through your characters to influence your audience?
        \n- <b>Where and when</b> does the story take place? Is this context/setting something that you audience could visualise themselves in? Does it fit to the problem/issue that you are trying to describe?
        \n- <b>How</b> do your characters/actors act and interact with each other? What state are they in? Will your audience be able to relate to this behavioural situation?
        \n- Are there any <b>specific constraints</b> you should consider that relate to the topic of the story that you should set?
        <!--
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Specific for Food: </b></font>
        \n- <b>Who</b> are they?
        -->
        \n\n<font color="#d21414">You can use the <b>topic field in your story form</b>  to start taking notes on making the story more relatable using its topic.</font>
    </string>
    <string name="lifestyle">Lifestyle</string>
    <string name="lifestyle_information">\nAs mentioned before, the <b>topic</b> of your story is very important in order for your audience to relate to it. Remember,
        a <b>more relatable story</b> is <b>more impactful</b> and <b>more persuasive</b> so your goal is to achieve exactly that. Try to make your audience immerse in your story and transport to your setting.
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Think of your audience: </b></font>
        \n- <b>Who</b> are they?
        \n- <b>Why</b> are they would be particularly interested in this topic?
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Think of your story: </b></font>
        \n- Who are the <b>characters</b> in your story? Can your audience relate to them? Will you be able to show desired and undesired behaviours through your characters to influence your audience?
        \n- <b>Where and when</b> does the story take place? Is this context/setting something that you audience could visualise themselves in? Does it fit to the problem/issue that you are trying to describe?
        \n- <b>How</b> do your characters/actors act and interact with each other? What state are they in? Will your audience be able to relate to this behavioural situation?
        \n- Are there any <b>specific constraints</b> you should consider that relate to the topic of the story that you should set?
        <!--
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Specific for Lifestyle: </b></font>
        \n- <b>Who</b> are they?
        -->
        \n\n<font color="#d21414">You can use the <b>topic field in your story form</b>  to start taking notes on making the story more relatable using its topic.</font>
    </string>
    <string name="business">Business</string>
    <string name="business_information">\nAs mentioned before, the <b>topic</b> of your story is very important in order for your audience to relate to it. Remember,
        a <b>more relatable story</b> is <b>more impactful</b> and <b>more persuasive</b> so your goal is to achieve exactly that. Try to make your audience immerse in your story and transport to your setting.
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Think of your audience: </b></font>
        \n- <b>Who</b> are they?
        \n- <b>Why</b> are they would be particularly interested in this topic?
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Think of your story: </b></font>
        \n- Who are the <b>characters</b> in your story? Can your audience relate to them? Will you be able to show desired and undesired behaviours through your characters to influence your audience?
        \n- <b>Where and when</b> does the story take place? Is this context/setting something that you audience could visualise themselves in? Does it fit to the problem/issue that you are trying to describe?
        \n- <b>How</b> do your characters/actors act and interact with each other? What state are they in? Will your audience be able to relate to this behavioural situation?
        \n- Are there any <b>specific constraints</b> you should consider that relate to the topic of the story that you should set?
        <!--
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Specific for Business: </b></font>
        \n- <b>Who</b> are they?
        -->
        \n\n<font color="#d21414">You can use the <b>topic field in your story form</b>  to start taking notes on making the story more relatable using its topic.</font>
    </string>
    <string name="sports">Sports</string>
    <string name="sports_information">\nAs mentioned before, the <b>topic</b> of your story is very important in order for your audience to relate to it. Remember,
        a <b>more relatable story</b> is <b>more impactful</b> and <b>more persuasive</b> so your goal is to achieve exactly that. Try to make your audience immerse in your story and transport to your setting.
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Think of your audience: </b></font>
        \n- <b>Who</b> are they?
        \n- <b>Why</b> are they would be particularly interested in this topic?
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Think of your story: </b></font>
        \n- Who are the <b>characters</b> in your story? Can your audience relate to them? Will you be able to show desired and undesired behaviours through your characters to influence your audience?
        \n- <b>Where and when</b> does the story take place? Is this context/setting something that you audience could visualise themselves in? Does it fit to the problem/issue that you are trying to describe?
        \n- <b>How</b> do your characters/actors act and interact with each other? What state are they in? Will your audience be able to relate to this behavioural situation?
        \n- Are there any <b>specific constraints</b> you should consider that relate to the topic of the story that you should set?
        <!--
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Specific for Sports: </b></font>
        \n- <b>Who</b> are they?
        -->
        \n\n<font color="#d21414">You can use the <b>topic field in your story form</b>  to start taking notes on making the story more relatable using its topic.</font>
    </string>
    <string name="travel">Travel</string>
    <string name="travel_information">\nAs mentioned before, the <b>topic</b> of your story is very important in order for your audience to relate to it. Remember,
        a <b>more relatable story</b> is <b>more impactful</b> and <b>more persuasive</b> so your goal is to achieve exactly that. Try to make your audience immerse in your story and transport to your setting.
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Think of your audience: </b></font>
        \n- <b>Who</b> are they?
        \n- <b>Why</b> are they would be particularly interested in this topic?
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Think of your story: </b></font>
        \n- Who are the <b>characters</b> in your story? Can your audience relate to them? Will you be able to show desired and undesired behaviours through your characters to influence your audience?
        \n- <b>Where and when</b> does the story take place? Is this context/setting something that you audience could visualise themselves in? Does it fit to the problem/issue that you are trying to describe?
        \n- <b>How</b> do your characters/actors act and interact with each other? What state are they in? Will your audience be able to relate to this behavioural situation?
        \n- Are there any <b>specific constraints</b> you should consider that relate to the topic of the story that you should set?
        <!--
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Specific for Travel: </b></font>
        \n- <b>Who</b> are they?
        -->
        \n\n<font color="#d21414">You can use the <b>topic field in your story form</b>  to start taking notes on making the story more relatable using its topic.</font>
    </string>
    <string name="security">Security</string>
    <string name="security_information">\nAs mentioned before, the <b>topic</b> of your story is very important in order for your audience to relate to it. Remember,
        a <b>more relatable story</b> is <b>more impactful</b> and <b>more persuasive</b> so your goal is to achieve exactly that. Try to make your audience immerse in your story and transport to your setting.
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Think of your audience: </b></font>
        \n- <b>Who</b> are they?
        \n- <b>Why</b> are they would be particularly interested in this topic?
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Think of your story: </b></font>- Who are the <b>characters</b> in your story? Can your audience relate to them? Will you be able to show desired and undesired behaviours through your characters to influence your audience?
        \n- <b>Where and when</b> does the story take place? Is this context/setting something that you audience could visualise themselves in? Does it fit to the problem/issue that you are trying to describe?
        \n- <b>How</b> do your characters/actors act and interact with each other? What state are they in? Will your audience be able to relate to this behavioural situation?
        \n- Are there any <b>specific constraints</b> you should consider that relate to the topic of the story that you should set?
        <!--
        \n\n<font color="#d21414"><b>Specific for Security: </b></font>
        \n- <b>Who</b> are they?
        -->
        \n\n<font color="#d21414">You can use the <b>topic field in your story form</b>  to start taking notes on making the story more relatable using its topic.</font>
    </string>

    <!-- End of Category/Topic Fragment -->

    <!-- -->
    <!-- End of -->

    <!-- -->
    <!-- End of -->
</resources>
